http://www.hsibaltimore.com/privacy

Health Sciences Institute - Official Site
Become a Member Now!
ACE Cancer Protocol
The Health Sciences Institute is intended to provide cutting-edge health information.
Nothing on this site should be interpreted as personal medical advice.
Always consult with your doctor before changing anything related to your healthcare.
Health Sciences Institute Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Last Updated: January 30, 2020
Institute for Health Sciences, LLC (“we,” “our,” or “us”) provides this privacy policy to describe how we collect, use, and share the information of individuals who visit our website at hsionline.com (the “Website”).    For more information about Institute for Health Sciences, LLC please visit www.hsionline.com
We know that your personal information is important to you and here at Institute for Health Sciences, LLC we are committed to ensuring it is kept secure and used carefully.
Below you will find a short summary of how and why we collect and use your data, who we share it with, and what we are doing to make sure your data is safe and secure.
What does Institute for Health Sciences, LLC do?
The Health Sciences Institute is an Institute for Health Sciences, LLC publication.
Institute for Health Sciences, LLC is a privately owned publishing company based in Baltimore, Maryland.  We publish newsletters which provide insight and advice on health.
We are part of a larger publishing group known as The Agora Companies (“group companies”). You can learn more about Institute for Health Sciences LLC in the “About Us” section of our Website.
What information do we collect and how is it used?
The information that we may collect about you broadly falls into two categories:
Information that you provide
We may ask you to provide personal information when you visit our Website, order forms and third-party websites where our advertisements are displayed, in order to provide our services to you.  This includes your contact details such as your name and email address.
We use that information to deliver your subscriptions and so you can register an account with us, giving you access to the subscriber-only areas of our Website.  We also use this information to personalize and improve your experience of our services, Website, and communications with you, and for advertising and marketing purposes, including sending you offers from selected partners.
You may also provide payment information to pay for subscriptions or use a one-click order process.
Information that we collect automatically
When you visit our Website and order forms, we may collect certain information automatically from your device.
The data we collect may include information like your IP address, device type, unique device identification numbers, browser-type, and other technical information.  We may also collect information about how your device has interacted with our Website or order form, including the pages accessed and links clicked. This data is collected using cookies and similar technology.
We collect this information so we can better understand the visitors who come to our Website and look at our order forms and what content may be of interest to them.  Using the information allows us to improve the quality and relevance of our Website and services.
Who does Institute for Health Sciences, LLC share your information with?
We may disclose your personal information to the following categories of recipients:
to our group companies who provide services to us, for example, enhancing the security of our Website, or processing personal information for the purposes described in this privacy policy or as described to you when we collect your personal information;
to third-party service providers who provide additional data processing services, for example, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, assisting with the processing of credit card payments, delivering your subscriptions, or personalizing and improving your experience with us;
to our group companies and to third parties (including, data resellers), so that they can market products and services we think may be of interest to you
as part of a corporate sale, merger, or acquisition, or other transfer of all or part of our assets, including as part of a bankruptcy proceeding;
to any competent law enforcement body, regulatory, government agency, or similar other third party where we believe disclosure is necessary as a matter of applicable law or regulation, or to exercise, establish or defend our legal rights or the rights of third parties; or
with your consent or as otherwise disclosed at the time of data collection or sharing.
Digital advertising & analytics
We may partner with ad networks and other ad serving providers (“Advertising Providers”) that serve ads on behalf of us and others on non-affiliated platforms.  Some of those ads may be personalized, meaning that they are intended to be relevant to you based on information Advertising Providers collect about your use of the Website and other sites or apps over time, including information about relationships among different browsers and devices.
We may also work with third parties that collect data about your use of the Website and other sites or apps over time for non-advertising purposes.  Institute for Health Sciences, LLC uses Google Analytics and other third-party services to improve the performance of the website and for analytics and marketing purposes.  For more information about how Google Analytics collects and uses data when you use our Website, visit www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners, and to opt out of Google Analytics, visit tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
Cookies
Cookies are small files placed on your hard drive by an internet server when you visit a website.  Some cookies can be used to identify your computer each time you visit a site.
Our Website uses cookies to allow authentication for access to the Subscriber Only areas of our sites.  This allows you to leave the site and come back without having to re-enter your email or user name and password every time.  We may also use cookies to track site usage, traffic patterns and to deliver ads for services we think will be of interest to you.
Your browser may offer tools to limit the use of cookies or to delete cookies; however, if you use these tools, our Website may not function as well as intended.
Third-party links and tools
Our Website may include hyperlinks to other websites that are not operated or controlled by us. This privacy policy only applies to our Website and we are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices of third-party websites.  You should review the privacy notices of other websites that you use to learn about their data practices.
The Website may also include integrated social media tools or “plug-ins,” such as social networking tools offered by third parties.  If you use these tools to share personal information or you otherwise interact with these features on the Website, these companies may collect information about you and may use and share such information in accordance with your account settings, including by sharing such information with the general public.  Your interactions with third-party companies and your use of their features are governed by the privacy notices of the companies that provide those features.  We encourage you to carefully read the privacy notices of any accounts you create and use.
Policy against advertising our Website using unsolicited email messages
We require that all third party e-mails promoting Hsionline.com or our products are sent only to those who have agreed to receive such messages. We prohibit any advertising of us and our websites using unsolicited email messages.  We will terminate our relationship with any third parties who do not comply with this policy.
If you feel you’ve been sent unsolicited emails promoting us or our websites and would like to register a complaint, please contact us by clicking here. We will immediately investigate your complaint.
Your choices
If at any time you wish to be removed from the Institute for Health Sciences, LLC mailing list, please click here to contact our customer service department.
We fund our free daily editorial email, The HSI eAlert by advertising our services and those of other group companies (occasionally we may carry advertising for a third-party service) within our editorial email, and by sending separate promotional emails.  There is an unsubscribe link in each of these emails and you can unsubscribe at any time.
Updates to this privacy policy
We may update this privacy policy from time to time in response to changing legal, technical or business developments. When we update our privacy policy, we will take appropriate measures to inform you, consistent with the significance of the changes we make.  We will obtain your consent to any material privacy policy changes if and where this is required by applicable data protection laws. You can see when this privacy policy was last updated by checking the “last updated” date displayed at the top of this privacy policy.
How to contact us
If you have any questions or concerns about our use of your personal information, please contact our Customer Service team.
Address:
Institute for Health Sciences, LLC
16W Madison Street
Baltimore, MD, 21201
Toll-free 1.888.213.0764
International +1.443.353.4240
Nevada Privacy Rights
Under Nevada law, Nevada residents may submit a request directing us not to make certain disclosures of personal information we maintain about them.
To exercise this right, please contact us:
Online at https://privacyportal-cdn.onetrust.com/dsarwebform/90ddaa87-9d70-4282-9d4f-d6cbd96bd224/a4b7da09-96d7-4faa-8468-aa659c80774b.html
California Privacy Rights
This section contains disclosures required by the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”) and applies only to “personal information” that is subject to the CCPA.  Consumers with disabilities may access this notice by contacting our customer service team at 1.888.213.0764.
Personal information we collect, disclose for a business purpose, and sell
We collect the categories of personal information about California consumers identified in the chart below.   In the past 12 months we have disclosed and sold California consumers’ personal information to third parties for business or commercial purposes – details are set out in the chart below.
Categories of Personal Information
Collected in the last 12 months:
Categories of sources from which information is collected:
Business or commercial purposes for collection, use, and sharing:
Disclosed for business purposes to the following categories of third parties:
Sold to the following categories of third parties:
Personal and online identifiers (such as first and last name, email address, or unique online identifiers)
Yes
All categories listed below.
All purposes listed below.
All categories listed below.
All categories listed below.
Categories of information described in Section 1798.80(e) of the California Civil Code (such as bank account number, credit card number, debit card number, or any other financial information, medical information, or health insurance information
Yes
All categories listed below.
All purposes listed below.
All categories listed below.
All categories listed below.
Characteristics of protected classifications under California or federal law (such as race or gender)
Yes
All categories listed below.
All purposes listed below.
All categories listed below.
All categories listed below.
Commercial or transactions information (such as records of personal property or products or services purchased, obtained or considered)
Yes
All categories listed below.
All purposes listed below.
All categories listed below.
All categories listed below.
Internet or other electronic network activity information (such as browsing history, search history, interactions with a website, email, application, or advertisement)
Yes
All categories listed below.
All purposes listed below.
All categories listed below.
All categories listed below.
Professional or employment-related information
Yes
All categories listed below.
All purposes listed below.
All categories listed below.
All categories listed below.
Education information
Yes
All categories listed below.
All purposes listed below.
All categories listed below.
All categories listed below.
Inferences drawn from the above information about your predicted characteristics and preferences
Yes
All categories listed below.
All purposes listed below.
All categories listed below.
All categories listed below.
Categories of sources
We collect this personal information from the following categories of sources:
Consumers
Service providers
Affiliates in our group companies
Consumer data resellers
Why we collect, use, and share California information
We use and disclose the personal information we collect for our commercial and business purposes as set out in this privacy policy.  These commercial and business purposes include, without limitation:
Our commercial purposes, including marketing, advertising, and enabling commercial transactions.
Our business purposes as identified in the CCPA, which include:
Auditing related to our interactions with you
Legal compliance
Detecting and protecting against security incidents, fraud, and illegal activity
Debugging
Performing services (for us or our service provider) such as account servicing, processing orders and payments, and analytics
Internal research for technological improvement
Internal operations
Activities to maintain and improve our services
Other one-time uses
Recipients of California Personal Information
We sell the categories of personal information listed above to the categories of third parties listed below:
Service providers
Affiliates in our group companies
Consumer data resellers
We disclose the categories of personal information listed above to the categories of third parties listed below for business purposes:
Service providers
Affiliates in our group companies
Advertising networks and consumer data resellers
Internet service providers
Data analytics providers
Operating systems and platforms
Social networks
Government entities, if required to do so
Your Rights Regarding Personal Information
California residents have certain rights with respect to the personal information collected by businesses.  If you are a California resident, you may exercise the following rights regarding your personal information, subject to certain exceptions and limitations:
The right to know the categories and specific pieces of personal information we collect, use, disclose, and sell about you; the categories of sources from which we collected your personal information; our purposes for collecting or selling your personal information; the categories of your personal information that we have either sold or disclosed for a business purpose; and the categories of third parties with which we have shared personal information.
The right to request that we delete the personal information we have collected from you or maintain about you.
The right to opt out of our sale(s) of your personal information. Please note that if you opt out of certain types of sales, we will be unable to provide you with the services that rely on such sales.
The right not to receive discriminatory treatment for the exercise of the privacy rights conferred by the CCPA.
To exercise any of the above rights, please contact us as follows:
By phone at 1.888.213.0764
On our website by clicking on the “Do Not Sell My Info” link or by clicking here
Verification Process and Authorized Agents
We may need to request additional information from you to verify your identity or understand the scope of your request, although you will not be required to create an account with us to submit a request or have it fulfilled.  At a minimum you will need to provide your name and email address.
You may designate an authorized agent to make a CCPA request on your behalf by informing our customer service team at 1.888.213.0764. You will need to provide your name and address, your agent’s name and address, and a copy of the document by which you appointed the agent.
Minors’ Right to Opt In
We do not knowingly sell the personal information of minors under 16 years of age.
Contact for More Information
If you have any questions or concerns about our use of your personal information, please contact our Customer Service team – https://www.newmarkethealth.com/misc/hsicontact/hsi_contact_form.htm
Address:
Institute for Health Sciences, LLC
16W Madison Street
Baltimore, MD, 21201
Toll-free 1.888.213.0764
International +1.443.353.4240
Want cutting-edge health news?
Want the latest health news delivered to your inbox every day?
Sign up below for The Health Sciences Institute’s free news service, the eAlert.
With the eAlert, you’ll discover the latest breakthroughs in medicine that you won’t hear about from the mainstream.
Doctor: We've Made A Huge Mistake with Coronavirus
A famous doctor just announced, "Almost no one would need to die from coronavirus."
He says that we've made a huge mistake in how we treat viruses.
If you're older or immune compromised, you need to hear what he has to say.
>>> Click here to see why he says no one should have died from coronavirus. <<<
MUST SEE: This Common Pill May Go Down As The Deadliest Ever.
Controversial report shows deadly prescription drugs used by over 9 million people.
One study says they're so deadly that they're already linked to OVER 106,000 deaths... and some are probably in your medicine cabinet right now.
Click here for the full story.
About Us
Privacy Policy
Terms and Conditions
SMS Terms and Conditions
Shop
Contact Us
Do Not Sell My Info
Copyright © 1997 - 2020
by Institute for Health Sciences, LLC16 W. Madison St, Baltimore, MD 21201, USA
By texting HSI to 855-909-0982, you are providing your electronic signature expressly consenting to be called and texted (including by prerecorded messages, using an autodialer, and/or automated means) with alerts, stories, reports, and marketing communications from Institute of Health Sciences, LLC. and its authorized representatives at the phone number you provide, including landlines and wireless numbers, even if the phone number is on a corporate, state or national Do Not Call list. You also consent and unconditionally agree to our Privacy Policy and Terms of Use, including the arbitration provision and class action waiver contained therein. Msg&data rates may apply. 15 Msgs/Month. You are not required to agree to this as a condition of making a purchase.
Terms & Conditions
The following Terms and Conditions apply to your use of the website located at hsionline.com (the “website”) and any text messages that you send to or receive from the Institute of Health Sciences, L.L.C. These Terms and Conditions constitute a binding agreement (“Agreement”) between you (“you”) Institute of Health Sciences, L.L.C (“we”, “us”, etc.)  Please read these terms carefully.
By providing your telephone number to us, texting us a short code listed on the website, or otherwise indicate your agreement to these Terms and Conditions, you are agreeing to the mandatory arbitration provision and class action waiver below.
ARBITRATION IS MANDATORY AND THE EXCLUSIVE REMEDY FOR ANY AND ALL DISPUTES RELATED TO THIS WEBSITE, THIS AGREEMENT, AND ANY TELEPHONE CALLS, EMAILS, OR TEXT MESSAGES THAT YOU RECEIVE FROM OR ON BEHALF OF US, UNLESS SPECIFIED BELOW OR UNLESS YOU OPT-OUT.
Text Messaging and Telemarketing Terms and Conditions
When you provide your telephone number on this website or send a text message to us with or from a short-code, you agree to receive alerts and communications, and marketing messages including those sent via automated telephone dialing system, text messages, SMS, MMS, and picture messages from Institute of Health Sciences, L.L.C at the phone number you provide on this website or the phone number from which you text the short code, including on landlines and wireless numbers, even if the phone number is on a corporate, state or national Do Not Call list. You also agree to the mandatory arbitration provision and class action waiver below. Your consent is not required to purchase goods or services. Message & data rates may apply.
You may opt-out at any time by texting the word STOP to the telephone number from which you receive the text messages.  Call 1-888-213-0764 to learn more.  By providing your telephone number, you agree to notify us of any changes to your telephone number and update your account us to reflect this change. Your carrier may charge you for text messages and telephone calls that you receive, or may prohibit or restrict certain mobile features, and certain mobile features may be incompatible with your carrier or mobile device. Contact your carrier with questions regarding these issues.
Dispute Resolution by Binding Arbitration and Class Action Waiver
Any dispute relating in any way to telephone calls, emails, or text messages that you receive from or on behalf of Institute of Health Sciences, L.L.C this website, or this Agreement (collectively “Disputes”) shall be submitted to confidential arbitration and shall be governed exclusively by the laws of the State of Maryland, excluding its conflict of law provisions.  For the avoidance of doubt, all claims arising under the Telephone Consumer Protection Act and state telemarketing laws shall be considered “Disputes” that are subject to resolution by binding individual, confidential arbitration.
If a Dispute arises under this Agreement, you agree to first contact us at 1-888-213-0764 or help@hsionline.com. Before formally submitting a Dispute to arbitration, you and we may choose to informally resolve the Dispute.  If any Dispute cannot be resolved informally, you agree that any and all Disputes, including the validity of this arbitration clause and class action waiver, shall be submitted to final and binding arbitration before a single arbitrator of the American Arbitration Association (“AAA”) in a location convenient to you or telephonically. Either you or we may commence the arbitration process by submitting a written demand for arbitration with the AAA, and providing a copy to the other party.  The arbitration will be conducted in accordance with the provisions of the AAA’s Commercial Dispute Resolutions Procedures, Supplementary Procedures for Consumer-Related Disputes, in effect at the time of submission of the demand for arbitration.  Except as may be required by law as determined by the arbitrator, no party or arbitrator may disclose the existence, content or results of any arbitration hereunder without the prior written consent of both parties. Institute of Health Sciences, L.L.C will pay all of the filing costs.  Without limiting the foregoing, YOU EXPRESSLY AGREE TO SUBMIT TO ARBITRATION ALL DISPUTES RELATING TO ANY TEXT MESSAGES OR TELEPHONE CALLS YOU RECEIVE FROM OR ON BEHALF OF US OR ANY ENTITY WITH WHOM WE MAY SHARE YOUR TELEPHONE NUMBER.  Further, we both agree that all entities with whom we share your telephone numbers shall be third party beneficiaries of this Agreement to Arbitrate Disputes, and that those entities have the same rights as Institute of Health Sciences, L.L.C to enforce this arbitration provision.
Notwithstanding the foregoing, the following shall not be subject to arbitration and may be adjudicated only in the state and federal courts of Maryland: (i) any dispute, controversy, or claim relating to or contesting the validity of our or one of our family company’s intellectual property rights and proprietary rights, including without limitation, patents, trademarks, service marks, copyrights, or trade secrets; (ii) an action by us for temporary or preliminary injunctive relief, whether prohibitive or mandatory, or other provisional relief; (iii) any legal action by us against a non-consumer; or (iv) interactions with governmental and regulatory authorities.  You expressly agree to refrain from bringing or joining any claims in any representative or class-wide capacity, including but not limited to bringing or joining any claims in any class action or any class-wide arbitration.
The arbitrator’s award shall be binding and may be entered as a judgment in any court of competent jurisdiction. To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, no arbitration under this Agreement may be joined to an arbitration involving any other party subject to this Agreement, whether through a class action, private attorney general proceeding, class arbitration proceedings or otherwise.
YOU UNDERSTAND THAT YOU WOULD HAVE HAD A RIGHT TO LITIGATE IN A COURT, TO HAVE A JUDGE OR JURY DECIDE YOUR CASE AND TO BE PARTY TO A CLASS OR REPRESENTATIVE ACTION.  HOWEVER, YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE TO HAVE ANY CLAIMS DECIDED INDIVIDUALLY AND ONLY THROUGH ARBITRATION.  You shall have thirty (30) days from the earliest of the date that you visit the website, the date you submit information to us through the website, or the date that you send a text message to us, to opt out of this arbitration agreement, by contacting us by email at help@hsionline.com or by mail Health Sciences Institute, PO Box 913, Frederick, MD 21705-0913. If you do not opt out by the earliest of the date that you visit the website, the date you submit information to us through the website, or the date that you send a text message to us, then you are not eligible to opt out of this arbitration agreement.
Electronic Signatures
All information communicated on the website is considered an electronic communication.  When you communicate with us through or on the website, by text message or telephone, or via other forms of electronic media, such as e-mail, you are communicating with us electronically.  You agree that we may communicate electronically with you and that such communications, as well as notices, disclosures, agreements, and other communications that we provide to you electronically, are equivalent to communications in writing and shall have the same force and effect as if they were in writing and signed by the party sending the communication.
You further acknowledge and agree that by clicking on a button labeled “ORDER NOW”, “SUBMIT”, “I ACCEPT”, “I AGREE”, “YES”, by texting a short code to us in response to a request on this website, or by clicking or similar links or buttons, you are submitting a legally binding electronic signature and are entering into a legally binding contract.  You acknowledge that your electronic submissions constitute your agreement and intent to be bound by this Agreement.  Pursuant to any applicable statutes, regulations, rules, ordinances or other laws, including without limitation the United States Electronic Signatures in Global and National Commerce Act, P.L. 106-229 (the “E-Sign Act”) or other similar statutes, YOU HEREBY AGREE TO THE USE OF ELECTRONIC SIGNATURES, CONTRACTS, ORDERS AND OTHER RECORDS AND TO ELECTRONIC DELIVERY OF NOTICES, POLICIES AND RECORDS OF TRANSACTIONS INITIATED OR COMPLETED THROUGH THE WEBSITE.  Furthermore, you hereby waive any rights or requirements under any statutes, regulations, rules, ordinances or other laws in any jurisdiction which require an original signature, delivery or retention of non-electronic records, or to payments or the granting of credits by other than electronic means You may receive a physical paper copy of this contract by contacting us at help@hsionline.com.
Privacy PolicyPlease read our Privacy Policy, which is incorporated herein by reference.  In the event of any conflict between these Terms and Conditions and the Privacy Policy, these Terms shall control.
Contact UsYou may contact us by telephone at 1-888-213-0764 or by email at help@hsionline.com.
